(Sheldon:)Leonard, come back.
Leonard, come back.
- What?
- Oh, of course.
(Sheldon:)It only works on the weak-minded.
(Leonard:)Good morning, sunshine.
Leonard, it's 8 a.m.
(Penny:)It's like the middle of the night.
(Leonard:)I know, but I have to go to work,
and I made you breakfast.
(Penny:)Oh, wow, that's so sweet.
(Penny:)- Hey, what's this?
- Before you open that...
(Leonard:)Um, are you familiar with the story
of the shoemaker and the elves?
(Penny:)Elves? Come on, Leonard,
it's too early for Lord of the Rings.
(Penny:)No, no.
Listen, once upon a time,
there was this shoemaker.
(Leonard:)And when he went to bed at night,
elves would sneak in...
(Leonard:)...and they would make
all these amazing shoes for him.
(Leonard:)And when the shoemaker
woke up in the morning...
(Leonard:)...he would be super happy.